Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. International Offices Records, 1929-1998 and undated RL.00716
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. International Offices records
1929-1998 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00716
25.56 Linear Feet
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT), founded in 1864, is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. Beginning with the opening of its London office in 1899, JWT has continually expanded its international activities, and currently operates out of over 200 offices in nearly 100 countries. The International Offices Records cover the years 1929-1998, with the bulk of materials dating from the 1970s-1980s. The collection primarily consists of financial records, correspondence, presentations, campaign drafts, account lists, meeting minutes and printed materials. Also includes slides from several presentations, videocassettes and audiocassettes. Countries and offices most heavily represented in the collection include Argentina (Buenos Aires), Australia (Sydney and Melbourne), Canada (Toronto and Vancouver), Colombia (Bogota), India (Bangalore, Calcutta, Madras, Mumbai, New Delhi), Japan (Tokyo), Mexico (Mexico City), Philippines (Manila), and Puerto Rico (San Juan). Client companies represented include: Air-India, Continental Airlines, Kodak, Ford, Hall's, Harayana Breweries, Kellogg's, Lotto, Nabisco, Nestlé, Oscar Mayer, Pepsi, Pizza Hut, Pond's (Unilever), and Warner-Lambert. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
19170 Items
Access Restrictions
RESTRICTED: Unpublished materials are closed to non-JWT researchers for 15 years from the date of creation.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to research until Use Copies can be produced. Contact Research Services staff for more information.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. International Offices Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a transfer in 1987 with additions in subsequent years.
Historical Note
Dates JWT International Offices Opened:
AFRICA
Egypt: Alexandria, 1927
South Africa: Cape Town, 1930
South Africa: Johannesburg/Sandton, 1932
South Africa: Port Elizabeth, 1928
ASIA/PACIFIC
Australia: Brisbane, 1984
Australia: Melbourne, 1929-1934, 1937
Australia: Perth, 1984
Australia: Sydney, 1929
Hong Kong, 1977
India: Bangalore, 1958-1959, 1979
India: Bombay, 1929
India: Calcutta, 1934
India: Madras, 1955
India: New Delhi, 1944
Indonesia: Jakarta, 1930, 1982
Japan: Osaka, 1931, 1957
Japan: Tokyo, 1956
Malaysia: Kuala Lumpur, 1975
New Zealand: Aukland, 1976
New Zealand: Wellington, 1930, 1974
Philippines: Manila, 1956
Singapore, 1978
Sri Lanka: Colombo, 1956, 1981
Taiwan: Taipei, 1983
Thailand: Bangkok, 1983
CANADA
Montreal, 1929
Toronto, 1911-1916, 1930
Vancouver, 1958
EUROPE
Austria: Vienna, 1930, 1960
Belgium: Antwerp, 1927
Belgium: Brussels, 1930, 1958
Denmark: Copenhagen, 1927, 1967
Finland: Helsinki, 1985
France: Paris, 1927-1940, 1949
Germany: Berlin, 1927
Germany: Düsseldorf, 1983
Germany: Frankfurt, 1952
Germany: Hamburg, 1983
Greece: Athens, 1974
Italy: Milan, 1951
Italy: Rome, 1962
Netherlands: Amsterdam, 1957
Netherlands: The Hague, 1928
Norway: Oslo, 1985
Poland: Warsaw, 1929
Portugal: Lisbon, 1929, 1967, 1973, 1981
Romania: Bucharest, 1929
Slovenia: 1993
Spain: Barcelona, 1932, 1966
Spain: Madrid, 1927, 1966
Sweden: Stockholm, 1927, 1969
Switzerland: Zug, 1964
Switzerland: Zurich, 1965
Turkey: Istanbul, 1930, 1985
United Kingdom: London, 1899-1916, 1919
United Kingdom: Manchester, 1980
LATIN AMERICA
Argentina: Buenos Aires, 1929
Bolivia: La Paz, 1978
Brazil: Rio de Janeiro, 1931
Brazil: São Paulo, 1929
Chile: Santiago, 1929, 1944
Colombia: Bogotá, 1944
Ecuador: Guayaquil, 1982
Ecuador: Quito, 1982
Mexico: Mexico City, 1943
Panama: Panama City, 1955
Puerto Rico: San Juan, 1955-1978
Uruguay: Montevideo, 1929
Venezuela: Caracas, 1955, 1964
JWT's first international office was set up in London in 1899. By 1923, it had opened six other European offices; by 1927, that number had doubled. Between 1927 and 1931, the company added additional offices in South Africa, India, Canada, Australia, Japan and South America. These offices were opened primarily so that advertisements could be geared more specifically to cultures of different regions.
Collection Overview
The International Offices Records cover the years 1929-1998, with the bulk of materials dating from the 1970s-1980s. The collection primarily consists of financial records, correspondence, presentations, campaign drafts, account lists, meeting minutes and printed materials. Also includes slides from several presentations, videocassettes and audiocassettes. Countries and offices most heavily represented in the collection include Argentina (Buenos Aires), Australia (Sydney and Melbourne), Canada (Toronto and Vancouver), Colombia (Bogota), India (Bangalore, Calcutta, Madras, Mumbai, New Delhi), Japan (Tokyo), Mexico (Mexico City), Philippines (Manila), and Puerto Rico (San Juan). Client companies represented include Air-India, Continental Airlines, Kodak, Ford, Kellogg's, Nabisco, Nestlé, Oscar Mayer, Pepsi-Cola, Pizza Hut, Pond's (Unilever), and Warner-Lambert.
Collection Arrangement
The collection is arranged into five series: General Office Files; Specific Offices; Oversize Materials; Audiovisual Materials; and Restricted Materials. The General Office Files Series includes account lists, newsletters, lists of accounts gained and lost, product categories, slides from JWT Worldwide presentations, and other materials concerning JWT international offices in general. The Specific Offices Series includes materials originating from specific JWT international offices, including reports of gains and losses, and changes in account status, as well as account lists, new business prospects and reports, newsletters, campaign presentations, account reviews and financial records, including several bound volumes of handwritten expense logs. The Audiovisual Materials Series includes primarily video cassettes of historical ad spots of JWT international offices clients. The Oversize Materials Series includes printed materials, newsletters, proofs, meeting photographs, financial records, memorabilia and campaign materials removed from previous series. The Restricted Materials Series contains materials not open to general researchers, due to a 15-year provision required of JWT collections.
Conditions Governing Access note
Unpublished materials are closed to non-JWT researchers for 15 years after the date of creation. In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to research until Use Copies can be produced. Contact Research Services staff for more information.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Account Files
International Advertisements Collection
Newsletters
Publications
Treasurer's Office Records
Writings and Speeches
Greg Bathon Papers
Frankfurt Office. Herbert Brungs Papers
Frankfurt Office. Harry Clark Papers
Howard Henderson Papers
Don Johnston Papers
Frankfurt Office. Denis Lanigan Papers
Samuel W. (Samuel Williams) Meek Papers
Thomas Sutton Papers
Shirley Woodell Papers
Advertising agencies -- Finance; Advertising agencies -- Colombia; Advertising agencies -- Canada; Advertising agencies -- Australia; Advertising agencies -- Argentina; Advertising agencies; Advertising campaigns; Audiocassettes; Videocassettes; Advertising agencies -- Philippines; Slides (photographs); Advertising agencies -- Puerto Rico; Advertising agencies -- Marketing; Advertising agencies -- Mexico; Advertising agencies -- India; Advertising agencies -- Japan; Nestlé; Nabisco, Inc.; Kellogg Company; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Warner-Lambert Company; Unilever (Firm); Pepsi-Cola Company; Eastman Kodak Company; Continental Airlines; J. Walter Thompson Company. Bangalore Office; Ford Motor Company; Air-India; J. Walter Thompson Company. Manila Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Melbourne Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Mexico City Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Mumbai Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Bogotá Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Buenos Aires Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Calcutta Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Madras Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Toronto Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Vancouver Office; J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. New Delhi Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. San Juan Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Sydney Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Tokyo Office
- General Office Files, 1944-1994 and undated, 11 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Series includes account lists, newsletters, lists of accounts gained and lost, product categories, and home addresses of JWT international employees and affiliates. Also includes several slide presentations relating to the company's overall international organization and performance, including maps, billings, and client alignment. Original folder titles were maintained and items were arranged alphabetically. Large-format items removed to Oversize Materials.
  - Account lists
    [Lists include fields for type of service; product; country; brand; local company name; date acquired; and JWT division.]
    - 1986, 8 folders (Box 1)
    - 1987-1988, 8 folders (Box 2)
    - 1988-1991, 9 folders (Box 3)
    - 1992, 8 folders (Box 4)
    - 1992-1993, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Advertising Age billings report, 1977-1980, 6 folders (Box 5)
    [Some items removed to Oversize Materials]
  - Caroline Demy files, 1981 (Box 6)
    [Caroline Demy served as JWT Vice President and International Media Director in charge of all multi-national media recommendations, programs, budgeting and national media planning for overseas offices.]
    - Argentina (Box 6)
    - Australia (Box 6)
    - Austria (Box 6)
    - Belgium (Box 6)
    - Bolivia (Box 6)
    - Brazil (Box 6)
    - Canada (Box 6)
    - Chile (Box 6)
    - Colombia (Box 6)
    - Denmark (Box 6)
    - Ecuador (Box 6)
    - England (Box 6)
    - France (Box 6)
    - Germany (Box 6)
    - Greece (Box 6)
    - Guatemala (Box 6)
    - Hong Kong (Box 6)
    - India (Box 6)
    - Italy (Box 6)
    - Japan (Box 6)
    - Malaysia (Box 6)
    - Mexico (Box 6)
    - Middle East (Box 6)
    - Netherlands (Box 6)
    - New Zealand (Box 6)
    - Paraguay (Box 6)
    - Peru (Box 6)
    - Portugal (Box 6)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 6)
    - South Africa (Box 6)
    - Spain (Box 6)
    - Sweden (Box 6)
    - Switzerland (Box 6)
    - Venezuela (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Clients Handled in Two or More Countries, 1990 Oct. (Box 7)
  - Clippings, 1944, 1978 and undated (Box 7)
  - Home address list, 1986 (Box 7)
  - International presentation, 1973, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Loss list, 1992 Jan. (Box 7)
  - Media Account Book, 1981, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Product categories, 1988, 1992, 1-3 of 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Product categories, 1988, 1992 (continued), 4 of 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Rolodex card files, undated (Box 9)
    [Includes entries for active and dropped clients, with information about company name changes, parent and subsidiary companies, office locations, and year of acquisition. Cards removed from the Rolodexes and placed in index card boxes.]
  - 130th birthday party in review, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Slides (Box 10)
    - Clients, 1992 and undated (Box 10)
      [Includes slide presentations for Le Pen, Heineken and Persil.]
    - JWT Europe presentation, undated (Box 10)
    - 1986 presentation, 5 folders (Box 10)
    - 1989 Worldwide slide presentation, 1988-1989, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - 1989 Worldwide slide presentation workbook (Box 11)
    - 1990 Worldwide presentation, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 1991 Worldwide presentation, 3 folders (Box 11)
    - 1992 Worldwide presentation, Red Dot slides, 2 folders (Box 11)
- Specific Offices and Countries, 1929-1998 and undated, 13 boxes
  Includes reports of gains and losses, and changes in account status, as well as account lists, new business prospects and reports, newsletters, campaign presentations, account reviews and financial records, including several bound volumes of handwritten expense logs and campaign proposals. Clients represented include Air-India, Continental Airlines, Kodak, Harayana Breweries, Nestlé, Pepsi, and Wills Cigarettes. Original folder titles were maintained and items arranged alphabetically, first by office, then by title. Large-format items have been removed to Oversize Materials.
  - Argentina (Box 12)
    - General, 1974-1980, 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Handbook, 1994 (Box 12)
    - Presentation to Executive Committee, 1973 Apr. 2 (Box 12)
    - Información de Medios, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Asia-Pacific, 1984 (Box 13)
    [Includes New Business Prospects and issues of MMAR Digest]
  - Australia
    - General, 1974-1985, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Australia Royal Commission of Inquiry into Drugs, 1978 Sept. (Box 13)
    - Report for JWT, 1981 July (Box 13)
  - Austria, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
    [Includes clippings, correspondence, and account lists]
  - Belgium, 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Bolivia, 1984 (Box 13)
    [Taquiña account status report]
  - Brazil (Box 14)
    [Some items removed to Oversize Materials.]
    - General, 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Cash and general ledgers, 1943-1953, 2 bound volumes (Box 14)
    - Clippings, 1991 and undated (Box 14)
    - Propoganda magazine, 1969 July (Box 14)
  - Canada
    - General, 1974-1985, 1-3 of 4 folders (Box 14)
    - General, 1974-1985 (continued), 4 of 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Board of Directors annual meeting, 1976 Apr. 27 (Box 15)
    - Board of Directors meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
    - Enterprise campaign, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
    - Office profiles, 1972, 1975, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Ownership report to legislation, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Presentation summary, 1973 Jan. 10 (Box 15)
  - Chile, 1978-1985 (Box 15)
  - Colombia
    - General, 1980-1985 (Box 15)
    - [Internal document explaining how to obtain international information through JWT network, 1998: Removed to Restricted Materials] (Box 15)
    - [Local work for Ford and Chicle Adams clients, 1997: Removed to Restricted Materials] (Box 15)
    - Newspaper articles mentioning Chris Jones and Andy Fenning's visit to Colombia, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Newspaper articles where James Evans (Managing Director) or Nuno Pais (Strategic Planning Director) are mentioned, 1997 (Box 15)
    - [Vision document prepared by James Evans, 1997: Removed to Restricted Materials] (Box 15)
  - Denmark, 1974-1985 (Box 15)
  - [Ecuador: Items removed to Oversize Materials.] (Box 15)
  - France
    - General, 1974-1985 (Box 15)
    - Aspects of Real presentation, 1992, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Germany (Box 16)
    - General, 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Cologne and Berlin Offices
      - Report of Investigation on Cold and Vanishing Creams--Consumers, 1929 Aug. (Box 16)
      - Report of Investigation on Cold and Vanishing Creams--Dealers, 1929 Aug. (Box 16)
  - Greece, 1975-1985 (Box 16)
  - Guatemala, 1975-1985 (Box 16)
    [Includes clippings, correspondence, and account lists. Some items removed to Oversize Materials.]
  - Hong Kong, 1978-1985 (Box 16)
  - India
    - General, 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Air India, Invention of a New Genre of Advertising: Non-Advertising, 1980 and undated (Box 17)
      [Includes billboard designs.]
    - Bombay and Karachi Offices, cash and general ledgers, 1946-1965, 4 bound volumes (Box 17)
    - List of clients, 1979 (Box 17)
    - Media Directors' Conference, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Nestlé Chocolates launch, Hijacking the Media, 1990 (Box 17)
      [Some items removed to oversize.]
    - Pepsi campaign, Innovation in Anticipation, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Printed matter, 1980-1995 (Box 17)
    - Rosy Pelican (Harayana Breweries) campaign, Rosy Pelican brief: Advertising with Audience Participation, undated (Box 17)
    - Stationery, undated (Box 17)
    - Wills Filter Tipped Cigarettes campaign, Making Metaphor Morph into Media, 1989 (Box 18)
  - Indonesia
    - General, 1975-1985 (Box 18)
    - Memoranda, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Israel, Tamir Cohen Advertising brochure, undated (Box 18)
  - Italy, 1974-1985, 3 folders (Box 18)
    [Includes clippings, correspondence, account lists, account status reports]
  - Japan
    - General, 1974-1985 (Box 18)
    - Cash and general ledger, 1959-1962 (Box 18)
    - Look at JWT Japan, circa 1984 (Box 19)
    - Media information, 1972-1974 (Box 19)
  - Korea, 1985 (Box 19)
    [Includes account lists]
  - Latin American and Caribbean regions, circa 1994 (Box 19)
  - [Includes media conference materials, speeches, press releases. Some Latin America items removed to Oversize Materials.] (Box 19)
  - Malaysia
    - General, 1976-1980 (Box 19)
    - Overview, circa 1989 (Box 19)
  - Mexico
    - General, 1974-1985, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Client Night invitations, 1994-1995 (Box 19)
    - Continental Airlines campaign, 1994-1995 (Box 19)
    - Emerging Decade, a Decade After presentation, 1994 (Box 19)
    - Kodak campaign, work terms and communication plan, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Mexico in the News packet, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
    - Nestlé campaign, Overview of Mexico Before and After the Crisis, 1995 (Box 20)
    - Regional profile, 1952 (Box 20)
  - Netherlands
    - General, 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - International seminar, 1975 (Box 20)
  - New Zealand, 1976-1985 (Box 20)
  - [North America (JWT Caribbean and Canada combined report): Removed to Oversize Materials.] (Box 20)
  - Norway, 1979 and undated (Box 20)
  - Paraguay, 1978-1985 (Box 20)
    [Includes billing reports and account lists]
  - Peru, 1974-1985, 3 folders (Box 20)
    [Includes correspondence, account status reports and account lists]
  - Philippines
    - General, 1974-1985, 1 of 4 folders (Box 20)
    - General, 1974-1985 (continued), 2-4 of 4 folders (Box 21)
    - Directors and Shareholders meetings, 1956-1961, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - How Will AFTAA Impact on Local Advertising presentation, 1993 May (Box 21)
    - Masagana Rice campaign, 1973-1978 (Box 21)
    - Office history, 1983 (Box 21)
    - Presidential Golden Plow Award for Public Service, 1974 (Box 21)
    - [Shareholders files, Vol. III, 1968-1972: Removed to Oversize Materials] (Box 21)
  - [Poland (Warsaw Office), Polish Society and Consumer Characteristics, 1996 Nov.: Removed to Restricted Materials] (Box 21)
  - Portugal
    - General, 1974-1985 (Box 21)
    - Credentials brochures, 1994 (Box 21)
  - Puerto Rico
    - General, 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Cash and general ledgers, 1956-1962, 1-5 of 6 bound volumes (Box 22)
    - Cash and general ledgers, 1956-1962 (continued), 6 of 6 bound volumes (Box 23)
    - Clippings honoring Enrique Martí Coll, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Corazón Adentro bulletin, 1992 (Box 23)
      [Issue honors the life of Enrique Martí Coll.]
    - Puerto Rico, Preliminary Prospects, 1969 Apr. 3 (Box 23)
  - Romania (Bucharest Office)
    - Report of Investigation on Eau de Cologne, 1930 (Box 23)
    - Report on Investigation on Lysoform Dealers, 1930 (Box 23)
  - Singapore, 1979-1985 (Box 23)
    [Includes correspondence and account lists]
  - Slovenia, Studio Marketing brochure, circa 1990 (Box 23)
  - South Africa
    - General, 1971-1985, 3 folders (Box 23)
    - Communications Plan, 1975 (Box 23)
    - Company and Communications Plan, 1977-1978, 1976, Dec. (Box 23)
  - Spain
    - General, 1973-1985, 1 of 2 folders (Box 23)
    - General, 1973-1985 (continued), 2 of 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Sri Lanka, 1980-1985 (Box 24)
  - Sweden (Stockholm Office), 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Switzerland, 1974-1980 (Box 24)
  - Thailand, 1980-1985 (Box 24)
  - Uruguay
    - General, 1978-1985 (Box 24)
    - Montevideo Office brochures and printed materials, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Venezuela
    - General, 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 24)
    - 25th Anniversary JWT Magazine, circa 1991 (Box 24)
- Oversize Materials, 6 boxes
  Series contains printed materials, newsletters, proofs, meeting photographs, financial records, memorabilia and campaign materials removed from previous series. Also includes one scrapbook compiled by Bob Doyer of the Amsterdam Office. Clients represented include Ford, Nestlé and Pond's. Items arranged first by size and then alphabetically by title.
  - Legal-size records
    - General files (Box 25)
      - All Countries Internal Statements, 1965, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - International at New York, Breakdown of Current Accounts and Net Assets, 1955-1957 (Box 25)
      - International Operations Equivalent Billing, Net Income, 1954-1956, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - Multinational Target Accounts, 1980 (Box 25)
    - Brazil, financial statements, 1966 (Box 25)
    - Canada, financial statements, 1969, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Latin America, storyboards, undated (Box 25)
    - North America, Consolidated Income Statement Detail (JWT Caribbean and Canada), 1963-1968, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Philippines (Box 26)
      - Board of Directors and Stockholders minutes, 1964-1961, 1970, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Shareholders files, Vol. III, 1968-1972 (Box 26)
  - Large-format materials
    - Advertising Age billings (international agency report), 1978 (Box 27)
    - Colombia, photographs taken during office meetings, 1996, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Ecuador, anniversary materials, 1996 (Box 27)
    - Germany (Frankfurt), Fokus Glas, circa 1996 (Box 27)
      [Brochure on office building where Frankfurt Office moved in 1996.]
    - Guatemala
      - 30th Anniversary album, 1988, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - 35th Anniversary album, 1993, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - India, Nestlé Chocolate launch, Hijacking the Media, 1990 (Box 27)
    - Japan, financial statements, 1969-1970, 7 folders (Box 28)
    - Mexico, Worldwide Operating Group meeting, 1994 Jun. 6 (Box 29)
    - Netherlands (Amsterdam), Bob Doyer scrapbook, 1998 (Box 29)
      [Photocopy of scrapbook compiled by Bob Doyer, former head of the JWT Amsterdam office. Includes materials dating from 1954-1975, including photographs, news clippings, proofs and tearsheets.]
    - Philippines (Box 30)
      - Clipping announcing Golden Plow Award, 1994 (Box 30)
      - Printed materials, 1987, 1998 (Box 30)
    - Uruguay, printed materials, undated (Box 30)
    - Venezuela, printed materials, 1982 and undated (Box 30)
    - Venezuela. Printed materials on office opening, 20th anniversary, 1964, 1985; 1 folders (Oversize-folder 1)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1992-1995 and undated, 2 boxes
  Series includes primarily video cassettes of historical ad spots of JWT international offices clients. Includes one audio cassette of an interview with John Holmes, JWT President of Latin America and the Caribbean. Clients represented include: Durex, Hall's, Kellogg's, Kodak, Lotto, Nabisco, Nestlé Oscar Mayer, Pepsi, Pizza Hut, and Warner Lambert. Items arranged alphabetically, first by office, then by title.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  RESTRICTED: Original audiovisual materials are closed to research until Use Copies can be produced. Contact Research Services staff for more information.
  - Brazil (Box 31)
    - AV1. Untitled. Format: VHS. Undated. (Box 31)